<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  SPDX-License-Identifier: FSFAP
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2022 Louis Schul <schul9louis@gmail.com>
 -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.klevernotes</id>
  <name>KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Akıllı Notlar</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKleverNotesxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KleverNotes 筆記</name>
  <summary>KleverNotes is a note taking and management application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">KleverNotes ne aplikace pro pořizování a správu poznámek</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">KleverNotes is a note taking and management application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">KleverNotes estas not-prena kaj -mastruma aplikaĵo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">KleverNotes es una aplicación para tomar notas y gestionarlas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">«KleverNotes» oharrak hartzeko eta kudeatzeko aplikazio bat da</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">KleverNotes on muistiinpanojen kirjoitus- ja hallintasovellus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">L'application KleverNotes est une application de prise de notes et pour leurs gestions.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">KleverNotes é unha aplicación para tomar e xestionar notas.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">KleverNotes הוא יישום לכתיבת וניהול פתקיות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">KleverNotes es un application per prender e gerer notas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">KleverNotes è un'applicazione per prendere appunti e gestire</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">KleverNotes ჩანიშვნისა და შენიშვნების მართვის აპლიკაციაა</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KleverNotes는 메모 작성 및 관리 앱입니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KleverNotes is een toepassing voor maken en beheren van notities </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">KleverNotes jest aplikacją do robienia i zarządzania notatkami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O KleverNotes é uma aplicação de gestão e registo de notas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">KleverNotes je aplikacija za vnašanje opomb in upravljanje</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">KleverNotes är ett antecknings- och hanteringsprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Not Alma ve Yönetme Uygulaması</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">KleverNotes — програма для створення нотаток та керування ними</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKleverNotes is a note taking and management applicationxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">KleverNotes 是一個筆記記錄與管理應用程式</summary>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer id="https://kde.org">
    <name>The KDE Community</name>
  </developer>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/office/klevernotes</url>
  <description>
    <p>KleverNotes is a note taking and management application for your mobile and desktop devices. It uses markdown and allow you to preview your content.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes per als vostres dispositius mòbils i d'escriptori. Empra el Markdown i permet previsualitzar el contingut.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes per als vostres dispositius mòbils i d'escriptori. Utilitza Markdown i permet previsualitzar el contingut.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KleverNotes is a note taking and management application for your mobile and desktop devices. It uses markdown and allow you to preview your content.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KleverNotes estas aplikaĵo por prenado kaj administrado de notoj por viaj porteblaj kaj labortablaj aparatoj. Ĝi uzas markdown kaj permesas vin antaŭrigardi vian enhavon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KleverNotes es una aplicación para tomar notas y gestionarlas para el escritorio y dispositivos móviles. Usa markdown y permite vistas previas del contenido.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«KleverNotes» oharrak hartzeko eta kudeatzeko aplikazio bat da, gailu mugikorretarako eta mahaigainekoetarako. «Markdown» erabiltzen du eta zure edukia aurrez ikusteko aukera eskaintzen dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KleverNotes on muistiinpanojen kirjoitus- ja hallintasovellus mobiili- ja työpöytälaitteille. Se käyttää Markdownia ja mahdollistaa sisällön esikatselun.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'application KleverNotes est une application de prises et de gestions de notes pour les périphériques mobiles et de bureau. Elle utilise le langage Markdown et vous permet d'avoir un aperçu de votre contenu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KleverNotes é unha aplicación para tomar e xestionar notas en dispositivos móbiles e de escritorio. Usa Markdown e ofrece unha vista previa do contido.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KleverNotes הוא יישום לכתיבת וניהול פתקיות למכשיר הנייד ולמחשב שלך. הוא משתמש ב־markdown ומאפשר לך לצפות בתוכן שלך בתצוגה מקדימה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KleverNotes es un application per prender e gerer notas per tu dispositivos mobile e de scriptorio. Illo usa markdown e te permitte vider preliminarmente tu contento.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KleverNotes è un'applicazione per prendere appunti e gestire i tuoi dispositivi mobili e desktop. Utilizza markdown e ti consente di visualizzare in anteprima i tuoi contenuti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KleverNotes ჩანიშვნისა და შენიშვნების მართვის აპლიკაციაა თქვენი მობილურისა და სახლის კომპიუტერისთვის. ის მარკდაუნს იყენებს და საშუალებას გაძლევთ, გადახედოთ შემცველობას, რომელიც თქვენ გეკუთვნით.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KleverNotes는 모바일 장치 및 데스크톱용 메모 작성 및 관리 앱입니다. Markdown 형식을 지원하며 내용을 미리 볼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KleverNotes is een toepassing voor maken en beheren van notities voor mobiele en bureaublad apparaten. Het gebruikt markdown en biedt u het bekijken van een voorbeeld van uw inhoud.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KleverNotes jest aplikacją do robienia i zarządzania notatkami dla urządzeń przenośnych i biurkowych. Używa markdown i umożliwia podgląd treści.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KleverNotes é uma aplicação para tirar e gerir notas no seu telemóvel e no seu computador. Use o Markdown e permite-lhe antever o seu conteúdo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KleverNotes je aplikacija za vnos opomb in upravljanje za vaše mobilne in namizne naprave. Uporablja markdown in dovoljuje predogled vaše vsebine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KleverNotes är ett antecknings- och hanteringsprogram för mobil och skrivbord. Det använder Markdown och låter dig förhandsgranska innehållet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Akıllı Notlar, taşınabilir ve masaüstü uygulamalarınız için bir not alımı ve yönetimi uygulamasıdır. Markdown kullanır ve içeriğinizi önizlemenize izin verir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KleverNotes — програма для створення нотаток та керування ними для ваших мобільних пристроїв та робочих станцій. У ній використано мову markdown та передбачено можливість попереднього перегляду результатів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKleverNotes is a note taking and management application for your mobile and desktop devices. It uses markdown and allow you to preview your content.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KleverNotes 是一個桌面與行動裝置用的筆記記錄與管理應用程式。它利用 Markdown 格式，並讓您能夠預覽您的內容。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main page on desktop</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina principal a l'escriptori</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina principal a l'escriptori</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní stránka na pracovní ploše</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefpaĝo en labortablo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página principal para el escritorio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page principale sur le bureau</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד ראשי בשולחן העבודה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina principale su desktop</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მთავარი გვერდი სამუშაო მაგიდაზე</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdpagina op bureaublad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavna stran na namizju</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Masaüstünde ana sayfa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Основна сторінка на робочій станції</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain page on desktopxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">桌面模式的主頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/klevernotes/main_note_desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Main page on small form factor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina principal al factor de format petit</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina principal al factor de format xicotet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefpaĝo en malgranda formfaktoro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página principal para factor de forma pequeño</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page principale sur périphérique de petit format</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד ראשי בדגם מוקטן</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagine principale su fattore di forma piccolo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მთავარი გვერდი პატარა ადგილას</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdpagina op kleine vormfactor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavna stran v majhni obliki</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Küçük biçimde ana sayfa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Основна сторінка з малим форм-фактором</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain page on small form factorxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">小螢幕模式的主頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/klevernotes/main_note_mobile.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Todo page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina de tasques pendents</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina de tasques pendents</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Stránka úkolů</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Paĝo de farendoj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página de tareas pendientes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page des tâches à faire</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד מטלות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina Da fare</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">განრიგის გვერდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Pagina te-doen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Stran stvari za še narediti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Yapılacaklar sayfası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Сторінка завдань</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTodo pagexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">待辦事項頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/klevernotes/todo_desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Drawing page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina de dibuix</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina de dibuix</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Stránka pro kreslení</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Paĝo de desegnado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página de dibujo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page de dessin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד ציור</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina di disegno</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">ხატვის გვერდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Pagina om op te tekenen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Stran risanja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Çizim sayfası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Сторінка малювання</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxDrawing pagexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">繪圖頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/klevernotes/painting.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.klevernotes.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2024-06-05">
      <description>
        <p>
          KleverNotes, KDE's Markdown note-taking and management application using Kirigami, is ready for its first release!
        </p>
        <p>
          KleverNotes allows you to create and preview a Markdown note while giving you the freedom to customize the preview from settings or using a CSS theme.
          You can organize your notes however you want with a combination of categories and groups, which will be directly reflected on your system in the 
          hierarchy of your KleverNotes storage folders.
          Simply choose your storage location and you're ready to write!
        </p>
        <p>
          You can print your notes, add small sketches and even create specific tasks for each of them, all from the application!
        </p>
        <p>
          Notes are saved as Markdown files in your KleverNotes storage for easy access. 
          They support the entire CommonMark specification with extensive syntax. 
          KleverNotes also introduces a small collection of opt-in “plugins” to extend basic markdown features, such as: 
          code highlighting, note linking, quick emoji, etc.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
