<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  SPDX-License-Identifier: FSFAP
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2022 Louis Schul <schul9louis@gmail.com>
 -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.klevernotes</id>
  <name>KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Akıllı Notlar</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KleverNotes</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKleverNotesxx</name>
  <summary>KleverNotes is a note taking and management application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">KleverNotes es una aplicación para tomar notas y gestionarlas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KleverNotes is een toepassing voor maken en beheren van notities </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O KleverNotes é uma aplicação de gestão e registo de notas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">KleverNotes je aplikacija za vnašanje opomb in upravljanje</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Akıllı Notlar, not alımı ve yönetimi uygulamasıdır</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">KleverNotes — програма для створення нотаток та керування ними</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKleverNotes is a note taking and management applicationxx</summary>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer_name>The KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Die KDE-Gemeinschaft</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">La Comunidad KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">De KDE gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">A Comunidade do KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Skupnost KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">KDE Topluluğu</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxThe KDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>KleverNotes is a note taking and management application for your mobile and desktop devices. It uses markdown and allow you to preview your content.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes per als vostres dispositius mòbils i d'escriptori. Empra el Markdown i permet previsualitzar el contingut.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KleverNotes és una aplicació de presa i gestió de notes per als vostres dispositius mòbils i d'escriptori. Utilitza Markdown i permet previsualitzar el contingut.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KleverNotes es una aplicación para tomar notas y gestionarlas para el escritorio y dispositivos móviles. Usa markdown y permite vistas previas del contenido.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KleverNotes is een toepassing voor maken en beheren van notities voor mobiele en bureaublad apparaten. Het gebruikt markdown en biedt u het bekijken van een voorbeeld van uw inhoud.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KleverNotes é uma aplicação para tirar e gerir notas no seu telemóvel e no seu computador. Use o Markdown e permite-lhe antever o seu conteúdo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KleverNotes je aplikacija za vnos opomb in upravljanje za vaše mobilne in namizne naprave. Uporablja markdown in dovoljuje predogled vaše vsebine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Akıllı Notlar, taşınabilir ve masaüstü uygulamalarınız için bir not alımı ve yönetimi uygulamasıdır. Markdown kullanır ve içeriğinizi önizlemenize izin verir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KleverNotes — програма для створення нотаток та керування ними для ваших мобільних пристроїв та робочих станцій. У ній використано мову markdown та передбачено можливість попереднього перегляду результатів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKleverNotes is a note taking and management application for your mobile and desktop devices. It uses markdown and allow you to preview your content.xx</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.klever.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
